beyondjane.com 2018-11-06

# Privacy Policy | BeyondJane

[Home](http://beyondjane.com/) » **Privacy Policy**

1\. General .

a. BeyondJane regards the privacy of your personal information very seriously. This Privacy Policy describes the manner in which BeyondJane treats and uses personal information that BeyondJane will receive and collect from you.

b. Personal information refers to information about you that is personally identifiable, as further detailed herein, that is provided by you and which is not otherwise publicly available.

c. Please review the ter ms of this Privacy Policy carefully. By accepting the Privacy Policy and the BeyondJane Standard Ter ms of Use you shall be deemed to have expressly consented to the use of your personal information in the manner described herein.

d. This policy may be revised by BeyondJane from time to time, and at any time. Any material changes will be effective only after BeyondJane will provide prior notice of the amended Privacy Policy at least 10 days in advance. Notice of the amended Privacy Policy may be given by general notice on the Web-Site ( http://www.beyondjane.com ) (the “ Site ”) or by e-mail. Any amended Privacy Policy will be clearly posted on the Site. If such changes will result in the use or disclosure of your personal information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time BeyondJane collected the information, you will have choice whether or nor BeyondJane shall use or disclose your information in accordance with the amended Privacy Policy. Notice of your choice not to disclose your information is to be delivered in the manner instructed on the Site.

e. This Privacy Policy applies to the practices of BeyondJane and its affiliates only. Other Web-Sites to which the Site is linked may be governed by their own privacy policies and statements, and BeyondJane is not and shall not be responsible for their operation, including but not limited to their information practices. Submission of information to or through these third party Web-Sites should be made by you after reviewing the privacy policies and statements of these sites.

2\. Information Collected .

a. BeyondJane collects personal information when you register with BeyondJane for the purpose of receiving BeyondJane’s newsletters.. BeyondJane may also collect personal information and/or install a “cookie” on your personal computer when you use, access or logon other products or services provided by BeyondJane, when you visit pages of certain partners of BeyondJane, and when you enter certain links or other promotional features on the Site.

b. Personal information which we will collect shall include information such as (but not limited to) your full name, email/IP address, and any such other general information BeyondJane may request.

c. The information collected by BeyondJane is used primarily for the delivery of BeyondJane newsletters, but may be used for other general purposes, such as trying to understand user preferences; customize promotional and advertising content users see;; improve services provided; contact users

d. BeyondJane may offer, from time to time, optional questionnaires, surveys and user services correspondences for the purpose of collecting information assessing users’ interests and needs (“Informative Data Requests”). Any use of any personal information collected in such Informative Date Requests shall be explained in advance and in detail.

3\. Use and Disclosure of Information .

a. BeyondJane collects, stores and processes your personal information on serves located in San Francisco, CA, USA. BeyondJane shall use your personal information for such purposes stated above in Section 2(e);

b. Unless otherwise expressly provided herein BeyondJane will not sell, lease or otherwise share or provide your personal information to any third parties, without your express permission. Notwithstanding the above, there may be certain circu ms tances in which some of your personal information will be shared with third parties, under strict restrictions, as further provided in this Privacy Policy.

c. BeyondJane may disclose personal information collected as provided herein:

(1) BeyondJane shall disclose information that it, in good faith, believes is appropriate to cooperate in investigations of suspected fraud or other illegal activity, situations involving potential threat to the physical safety of any person, or to conduct investigations of violation of its Publishing Agreement; or any such similar information.

(2) BeyondJane shall disclose information in response to a subpoena, warrant, court order, levy, attachment, or any comparable or applicable process; or otherwise to establish or exercise BeyondJane’s legal rights or to defend against legal clai ms .

(3) BeyondJane may share information with or disclose information to its employees, officers, directors, consultants, advisors, subsidiaries, affiliates, business partners, joint ventures, provided such disclosure is on a need-to-know basis, and subject to confidentiality provisions.

(4) BeyondJane may share aggregated statistic data provided such information is not connected with personally identifiable data.

(5) In the event that v is merged with or acquired by another entity, the successor entity will have access to the information maintained by BeyondJane. In such case the successor entity shall continue to be bound by the provisions of this Privacy Policy, unless and until amended in accordance with the provisions in this Privacy Policy.

(6) We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

4\. Communications .

a. BeyondJane will generally communicate with its users via email. BeyondJane further reserves the right to use your email address to send you other communications, such as periodic newsletters, user questionnaires and surveys, and any other communications.

b. You will be able to choose whether to receive these communications, in whole or in part, upon completing a standard registration form, or at any time thereafter, by changing your preferences as instructed on the Site.

5\. Changing your Information .

You can review the personal information you have provided us and make any desired changes to such information including deleting information, at any time, by changing the preferences and information as instructed on the Site.

6\. Security .

BeyondJane is committed to handling your personal information with the highest standards of security information. BeyondJane shall maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to maintain the secrecy of the personal information, and will test its security syste ms regularly.

7\. Contact .

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or your dealings with BeyondJane, you can contact us at: +97236440435 Monday through Thursday between 10:00 – 18:00 GMT, or write to as at webmaster@beyondjane.com .
